This is a Live set powered by Fadercraft Control.
Fourteen channels. Six controls each.
Instant access throughout your project.
The whole set sits on two pages.
Hold to peek at the other page
and release to return.
Turn the encoder to switch and stay.
The same interaction pattern
carries across every channel.
Each channel gives you six controls
across two encoder banks.
Hold to peek at the other bank
and release to return.
Turn the encoder to switch and stay.
You've been mixing. Now play.
One button drops you into the last
instrument you touched,
right where you left it.
Press the button again,
and you're back to the mixer
on the exact page you were working on.
Your workflow stays uninterrupted.
DAW Mixer and DAW Control
are always within reach.
Switch between native modes with a single
hotkey — or any key you assign.
The same mapping concept carries
across pages, banks, and instrument jumps.
You define how navigation works once,
and it stays consistent under your fingers.
Everything adapts to your workflow.
14 channels. Six controls per channel.
Designed for muscle memory.
One workflow for production,
mixing, and live performance.
This is Fadercraft Control XL.
Stay in the music.